[{"answer": "my friend, this is gonna be hard, but I wanted it to come from me, and nobody else", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "It's me, I've been sleeping with your wife", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "So you can like, bite, and pull people's hair and stuff", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What's fish hooking", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Well that was depressing, I think I just bought a soft pretzel from one of the kids from Fame.  Ready to go to the movies", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "This is my friend?  This is my friend?  You're my friend? u000bmy frien", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know, I hardly ever say that about people", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well I'm sorry, I thought you said it was okay", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well, you're not gonna get going are you", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, no.  But..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well let me ask you a question.  Am I the Ultimate Fighting Champion", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Well I'm not gonna stop until I'm the Ultimate Fighting Champion", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You didn't know that already", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Okay, just get a lot better.  Fast", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend!", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Come on my friend, look at that!  They are not breaking up, look at them.  Okay that's, you know what that is?  That is a, that is a second date, that's what that is!  Look at that, she just put her hand on his thigh..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Ohh!  my friend, this is all your fault!  Now he loves her, he's gonna marry her, and this is all your fault", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You said she was bald!", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Y'know I have a torn rotator cuff, a hairline fracture in my right forearm, and a severely bruised my friend's that place, but that   really   hurt", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well if you're asking me to quit, then you're asking me to be someone I'm not.  I've got to do this", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well then, y'know what?  I care about you to much to watch you hurt yourself like this.  So if you have to do this, then you're gonna have to do it without me", "docId": "324ufc.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Then I've gotta go.  Bye.", "qsentId": 22}]